<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Histories on ASF Community Development</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/history/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Histories on ASF Community Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ComDevBoardResolution</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/history/boardresolution.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/history/boardresolution.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Apache Community Development Project was created in November 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code panel&#34; style=&#34;border-style: solid;border-width: 1px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeHeader panelHeader&#34; style=&#34;border-bottom-width: 1px;border-bottom-style: solid;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;b&gt;Board Resolution Creating the Apache Community Development Project&lt;/b&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeContent panelContent&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;   Establish the Apache Community Development Project&#xA;&#xA;   WHEREAS, the Board of Directors deems it to be in the best&#xA;   interests of the Foundation and consistent with the&#xA;   Foundation&#39;s purpose to establish a Project Management&#xA;   Committee charged with coordinating community development&#xA;   efforts.&#xA;&#xA;   NOW, THEREFORE, BE IT RESOLVED, that a Project Management&#xA;   Committee (PMC), to be known as the &amp;quot;Apache Community&#xA;   Development Project&amp;quot;, be and hereby is established&#xA;   pursuant to Bylaws of the Foundation; and be it further&#xA;&#xA;   RESOLVED, that the Apache Community Development Project&#xA;   be and hereby is responsible for helping people become&#xA;   involved with Apache projects; and be it further&#xA;&#xA;   RESOLVED, that the office of Vice President, Apache Community&#xA;   Development Project, be and hereby is created, the person&#xA;   holding such office to serve at the direction of the Board&#xA;   of Directors as the chair of the Community Development PMC,&#xA;   and to have primary responsibility for management of the&#xA;   projects within the scope of the Apache Community Development&#xA;   project; and be it further&#xA;&#xA;   RESOLVED, that the persons listed immediately below be and&#xA;   hereby are appointed to serve as the initial members of the&#xA;   Apache Community Development Project PMC:&#xA;&#xA;   * Ross Gardler &amp;lt;rgardler@apache.org&amp;gt;&#xA;   * Luciano Resende &amp;lt;lresende@apache.org&amp;gt;&#xA;   * Santiago Gala &amp;lt;sgala@apache.org&amp;gt;&#xA;   * Bertrand Delacretaz &amp;lt;bdelacretaz@apache.org&amp;gt;&#xA;   * Ted Dunning &amp;lt;tdunning@apache.org&amp;gt;&#xA;   * Noirin Shirley &amp;lt;noirin@apache.org&amp;gt;&#xA;&#xA;   NOW, THEREFORE, BE IT FURTHER RESOLVED, that Ross Gardler&#xA;   be appointed to the office of Vice President, Apache Community&#xA;   Development Project, to serve in accordance with and&#xA;   subject to the direction of the Board of Directors and&#xA;   the Bylaws of the Foundation until death, resignation,&#xA;   retirement, removal or disqualification, or until a successor&#xA;   is appointed; and be it further&#xA;&#xA;   RESOLVED, that the initial Apache Community Development PMC&#xA;   be and hereby is tasked with the creation of a set of bylaws&#xA;   intended to encourage open participation in the Apache&#xA;   Community Development Project.&#xA;&#xA;   Special order 3A, establish the Apache Community Development Project,&#xA;   was approved by Unanimous Vote of the directors present.&#xA;&#xA;   Furthermore, the board requested that this PMC take over the&#xA;   stewardship of the community@ and women@ mailing lists.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot Mentoring Programme with India ICFOSS</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/history/mentoringprogramme-icfoss-pilot.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/history/mentoringprogramme-icfoss-pilot.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note that this information is about a pilot program that&#xA;happened back in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ASF has been participating in many mentoring initiatives, and it&amp;rsquo;s now&#xA;partnering in a pilot project with India ICFOSS to provide mentoring for&#xA;undergraduate and graduate students that have interest in learning how&#xA;to participate in open source communities at ASF.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The mentoring programme is not here to teach you to write documentation or&#xA;code. It is here to help you understand how to make a valuable contribution&#xA;to an Apache project. You can expect to be guided through our contribution&#xA;processes. You can also expect to get technical support with respect to&#xA;your chosen project. You cannot expect your mentor to be a &amp;ldquo;teacher&amp;rdquo;, they&#xA;will provide enough information for you to progress within the project. You&#xA;need to bring the confidence to take their guidance and discover the detail&#xA;for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
