<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mentoring on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/mentoring.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in mentoring on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/mentoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GSoC admins</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/gsoc-admin-tasks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/gsoc-admin-tasks.html</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive guide to being a GSoC admin for the ASF
List of duties:
Make sure the ASF has an extensive list of project ideas ready shortly after Google announces the program (around the end of January). Projects must create Jira issues for their ideas and label them with gsoc&amp;lt;year&amp;gt;; and mentor. If a project doesn&amp;rsquo;t use Jira, have them create the ideas in the GSOC Jira project. Create a Jira filter for these ideas to use in the application (see next).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/</guid>
      <description>Mentoring &amp;para; A major job of Community Development is mentoring. Mentoring is the process of actively bringing someone along in a discipline - investing your time into influencing the future. Time spent mentoring today will pay off for years to come.
Anyone can be a mentor. You just have to take a moment to encourage someone else to participate.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some concrete ways you can provide mentoring to other members of your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring a new committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/committer.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/committer.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring a new committer &amp;para; So I&amp;rsquo;m a committer now. What&amp;rsquo;s next? What rights do I have now that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have before? What are the social conventions around making a commit?
These things vary from one project to another, so clearly documenting them for your particular project is critical.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the basics that are true across (almost) all Apache projects.
TODO
Outline:
Encouraging other contributors Good commit messages Becoming a PMC member </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring a new PMC member</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/pmc.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/pmc.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring a new PMC member &amp;para; So I&amp;rsquo;m a PMC member now. What does this mean? What rights do I have now that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have before? What conversations belong on the private list, as opposed to the public list.
These things vary a little from one project to another, so clearly documenting them for your particular project is critical. And specifically assigning a PMC mentor to new PMC members can greatly help that new member get up to speed, and prevent problems in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring Mentors</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/mentor.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/mentor.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring Mentors &amp;para; The job of a mentor is to reproduce - spread the work load. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve mentored someone, you need to encourage them to become a mentor themselves. Here&amp;rsquo;s some ways you can do that.
Point out people that need a little help Encourage them to answer a question rather than answering it yourself &amp;hellip; TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring: First Patch</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/firstpatch.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/firstpatch.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring: First Patch &amp;para; A beginner&amp;rsquo;s first patch on a project can be an intimidating and frustrating experience. Clearly documenting the entire process from checkout to accepted patch greatly lowers the barrier for a new contributor, and makes it more likely that they&amp;rsquo;ll come back for their second patch.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some tips on how to do that.
Outline:
Talk to the project first Make sure it&amp;rsquo;s wanted/welcome See if there&amp;rsquo;s already work in progress, or suggestions Find someone to be your advocate Finding the source Writing a good commit message Following up on your pull request Learning from your struggle: Improving the documentation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilot Mentoring Programme with India ICFOSS</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/history/mentoringprogramme-icfoss-pilot.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/history/mentoringprogramme-icfoss-pilot.html</guid>
      <description>Note that this information is about a pilot program that happened back in 2013.
The ASF has been participating in many mentoring initiatives, and it&amp;rsquo;s now partnering in a pilot project with India ICFOSS to provide mentoring for undergraduate and graduate students that have interest in learning how to participate in open source communities at ASF.
The mentoring programme is not here to teach you to write documentation or code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
