<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>governance on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/governance.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in governance on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/governance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Maturity Model for Apache Projects</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/apache-way/apache-project-maturity-model.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/apache-way/apache-project-maturity-model.html</guid>
      <description>The Apache Project Maturity Model provides a suggested framework for evaluating the overall maturity of an Apache project community and the codebase that it maintains. While this model is specific to projects of the Apache Software Foundation (ASF), many of these factors apply to any open source project.
Overview &amp;para; The goals of this maturity model are to describe how Apache projects operate in a concise and high-level way, and to provide a basic framework that projects may choose to use to evaluate themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMC Responsibilities</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/responsibilities.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/responsibilities.html</guid>
      <description>The Project Management Committee (PMC) is responsible for the oversight of the project, including technical decisions, ensuring that the project is operating in accordance with ASF norms, adding new members to the project, and voting on releases.
Conducting business Ensuring project health Adding community members Reporting Conducting Business &amp;para; The PMC is expected to conduct all of its business on the public developers mailing list, in the full view of the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Independence</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/projectIndependence.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/projectIndependence.html</guid>
      <description>While not all ASF projects practice all aspects of the Apache Way in the same way, there are a number of rules and policies that Apache projects must follow – things like complying with PMC release voting, legal policy, brand policy, using mailing lists, etc., which are documented in various places.
A community is not merely a set of rules; it is also a set of behaviors that the participants express when interacting within that community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
