<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>navigation on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/navigation.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in navigation on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/navigation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ASF Community Development Blog</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/blog/</guid>
      <description>ASF Community Development Blog &amp;para; Contributions to this blog are welcome!
We are looking for posts related community building, community-related success or failure stories and related topics.
Posts &amp;para; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committer resources</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of useful Apache tools and services available for Apache projects and committers. This is a brief set of pointers or signposts to that information.
Apache Infrastructure Information &amp;para; The primary portals for Apache Infra questions - how Subversion/Git/Websites, etc. work at the ASF - are pages at apache.org/dev and infra.apache.org.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a committer, you can patch this very website yourself!
Decision making &amp;para; Decisions in Apache projects result from:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Development: What we do</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Community Development: What We Do &amp;para; The Community Development (ComDev) project provides a wide array of information, FAQs, and help to newcomers and existing committers, and maintains a number of helpful tools.
Community Development: What We Do Mentoring for Individuals and Help Getting Around Mentoring for Projects Education + Outreach Diversity Conference Travel Assistance Tools and Code we Maintain Physical artifacts About This Website Mentoring for Individuals and Help Getting Around &amp;para; GSoC Contributors Guide Committers Guide Project Management Committees Mentoring for Projects &amp;para; Incubator Mentors - Many folks here are IPMC members or mentors, too Get community advice on dev@community Education + Outreach &amp;para; ApacheCon Partnered Industry Events (FOSDEM etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to the Apache Software Foundation</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</guid>
      <description>This page is for people who are reasonably comfortable with open source development models but need a helping hand finding their way around the Apache Software Foundation and our way of developing software (commonly called &amp;ldquo;The Apache Way&amp;rdquo;). For those wishing to start from the very beginning, we have a newcomers page.
Project Independence And Policies &amp;para; While not all ASF projects practice all aspects of the Apache Way in the same way, there are a number of rules that Apache projects must follow – things like complying with PMC release voting, legal policy, brand policy, using mailing lists, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/links.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/links.html</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of links to information that&amp;rsquo;s relevant to the Apache Way and Open Source in general.
Note that most of these links point to websites that are outside of the control of the Apache Software Foundation. Please contact their respective authors for more information or questions. General discussion on the dev@community.a.o list is fine of course.
Books &amp;para; Producing Open Source Software - by Karl Fogel Blog posts &amp;para; Apache - the Switzerland of Open Source?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/</guid>
      <description>Mentoring &amp;para; A major job of Community Development is mentoring. Mentoring is the process of actively bringing someone along in a discipline - investing your time into influencing the future. Time spent mentoring today will pay off for years to come.
Anyone can be a mentor. You just have to take a moment to encourage someone else to participate.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some concrete ways you can provide mentoring to other members of your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Committees</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/</guid>
      <description>The Project Management Committee, or PMC, is the technical steering committee for a project. This group determines the roadmap for the project, decides who will be added as committers and PMC members, and reports quarterly to the Board of Directors.
The Board expects all PMCs to understand and comply with published policies.
PMC Responsibilities Chair Voting Reporting Adding committers Adding PMC members What to do as a new member PMC Responsibilities &amp;para; The PMC is responsible for the management of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking about Apache, our Projects and our Community</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/speakers/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for speakers for an event, or are a speaker looking for materials, this is the place for you.
If you are seeking to organise an Apache-branded event, you must ensure your activities conform to the Third Party Event Branding Policy. Once you have verified you are in conformance, please consider adding your event to the events calendar.
Finding speakers &amp;para; You can use our &amp;ldquo;Find People&amp;rdquo; application to find speakers willing and able to talk about The Apache Software Foundation and its projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome, Apache newcomers!</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newcomers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newcomers/</guid>
      <description>In this section we&amp;rsquo;ll help you take your first steps as an open source developer in one of our many Apache project communities. As an all-volunteer run organization, Apache and the many Apache projects rely on people like you stepping up to help out.
Where do I start? - a guide to your first engagement with an Apache project How should I behave? - etiquette and codes of conduct at Apache Newbie FAQ - some commonly asked questions (and their answers) How many projects are at Apache?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
