<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>newcomers on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/newcomers.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in newcomers on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/newcomers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apache Newcomer FAQs</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newbiefaq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newbiefaq.html</guid>
      <description>These answers to frequently asked questions may help newcomers to The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) and our many Apache projects understand how we work.
Index of Questions
About The Apache Software Foundation How do I find projects or technologies at the ASF? How are projects managed at the ASF? How do I ask a question about the ASF in general? How do I get user support for an Apache project? Getting involved with Apache projects How do I choose an Apache project to work on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/becomingacommitter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/becomingacommitter.html</guid>
      <description>Read the mailing list Contribute code (and other things) End user support Documentation Review PRs and tickets Be visible Test, and vote on releases (non-binding) Give talks Disclaimer &amp;para; Nothing in this post should be construed as a guarantee. You can do everything listed here, for years, and still not become a committer. This is because the decision is made by individuals on the project PMC, who do things for their own reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gettingStarted/101.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gettingStarted/101.html</guid>
      <description>Where do I start? &amp;para; If you have no idea where to start your engagement with an Apache project, this is the page for you.
Finding the right project &amp;para; The key to working on projects at Apache (and on any open source project, for that matter) is to have a personal reason for being involved. You might be trying to solve a day job issue or learn a new technology, or simply want to do something fun in your free time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring: First Patch</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/firstpatch.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/firstpatch.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring: First Patch &amp;para; A beginner&amp;rsquo;s first patch on a project can be an intimidating and frustrating experience. Clearly documenting the entire process from checkout to accepted patch greatly lowers the barrier for a new contributor, and makes it more likely that they&amp;rsquo;ll come back for their second patch.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some tips on how to do that.
Outline:
Talk to the project first Make sure it&amp;rsquo;s wanted/welcome See if there&amp;rsquo;s already work in progress, or suggestions Find someone to be your advocate Finding the source Writing a good commit message Following up on your pull request Learning from your struggle: Improving the documentation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome, Apache newcomers!</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newcomers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newcomers/</guid>
      <description>In this section we&amp;rsquo;ll help you take your first steps as an open source developer in one of our many Apache project communities. As an all-volunteer run organization, Apache and the many Apache projects rely on people like you stepping up to help out.
Where do I start? - a guide to your first engagement with an Apache project How should I behave? - etiquette and codes of conduct at Apache Newbie FAQ - some commonly asked questions (and their answers) How many projects are at Apache?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
