<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calendars on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/calendars.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Calendars on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/calendars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apache Conferences Calendar</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/calendars/conferences.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/calendars/conferences.html</guid>
      <description>Deprecated - See New Calendar instead This calendar is no longer maintained; please see this page instead.
This Calendar is maintained by the Apache Community Development Committee (ComDev), to have your event listed considered for addition please mail dev@community.apache.org. Note that to be listed in this calendar events must conform to the Third Party Event Branding Policy.
Upcoming events List loading This Calendar is also available as an iCal feed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Related Event Calendars</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/calendars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/calendars/</guid>
      <description>This calendar lists major events relating to The Apache Software Foundation and our many Apache projects. We also have an automated listing of upcoming Apache-related Meetups (smaller events) available.
This Calendar is maintained by Apache Community Development volunteers (ComDev); to have your event listed considered for addition please mail dev@community.apache.org. Note that to be listed in this calendar events must already conform to the Third Party Event Branding Policy and have been approved by either the relevant Apache PMC or the Branding Committee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
