<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>committers on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/committers.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in committers on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/committers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding Committers</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-committers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-committers.html</guid>
      <description>The addition of new committers is essential to the long-term sustainability of an open source project. The PMC is responsible for determining who will be added as a committer.
Who should be a committer? Vote process What to do when a committer is elected Note: Formal policy/process document is here: https://www.apache.org/dev/pmc.html#committer-management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASF Contributor Ladder</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributor-ladder.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributor-ladder.html</guid>
      <description>Projects at the ASF offer a way to grow in your responsibilities in the project, from being a user, all the way up to being a maintainer of the project. While the specific details may look different from one project to another, the rungs of the ladder look mostly the same.
User Contributor Committer PMC Member ASF Member Officers of the Foundation Board of Directors User &amp;para; Everything that we do in an ASF project is for the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/becomingacommitter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/becomingacommitter.html</guid>
      <description>Read the mailing list Contribute code (and other things) End user support Documentation Review PRs and tickets Be visible Test, and vote on releases (non-binding) Give talks Disclaimer &amp;para; Nothing in this post should be construed as a guarantee. You can do everything listed here, for years, and still not become a committer. This is because the decision is made by individuals on the project PMC, who do things for their own reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committer resources</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of useful Apache tools and services available for Apache projects and committers. This is a brief set of pointers or signposts to that information.
Apache Infrastructure Information &amp;para; The primary portals for Apache Infra questions - how Subversion/Git/Websites, etc. work at the ASF - are pages at apache.org/dev and infra.apache.org.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a committer, you can patch this very website yourself!
Decision making &amp;para; Decisions in Apache projects result from:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring a new committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/committer.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/committer.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring a new committer &amp;para; So I&amp;rsquo;m a committer now. What&amp;rsquo;s next? What rights do I have now that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have before? What are the social conventions around making a commit?
These things vary from one project to another, so clearly documenting them for your particular project is critical.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the basics that are true across (almost) all Apache projects.
TODO
Outline:
Encouraging other contributors Good commit messages Becoming a PMC member </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newcommitter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newcommitter.html</guid>
      <description>Identifying potential new committers, calling a vote for their recognition as a committer and processing the relevant documents are tasks to which the whole community can contribute.
Each project has a different approach to managing new committers. This page describes a common process found in many Apache projects. It also provides drafts for the various communications that are necessary.
Guidelines for assessing new candidates for committership Ability to work cooperatively with peers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
