<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apache Community Development - Welcome on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apache Community Development - Welcome on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/proposals/ZestProposal.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/proposals/ZestProposal.html</guid>
      <description>title: Zest Proposal
Abstract  qi4j = new Energy4Java();  That is how to create the Qi4j runtime, and it captures the essence of its spirit. Qi4j is a platform to develop Composite Oriented Programming applications in Java in a new, exciting and productive manner.
Governance of Provisional Top Level Project Provisional Top Level Project is a new idea at the ASF, and the Qi4j community is willing to try the idea, instead of simply debating it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Maturity Model for Apache Projects</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/apache-way/apache-project-maturity-model.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/apache-way/apache-project-maturity-model.html</guid>
      <description>The Apache Project Maturity Model provides a suggested framework for evaluating the overall maturity of an Apache project community and the codebase that it maintains. While this model is specific to Apache projects (i.e. hosted at the ASF) many of these factors are important for any open source project.
Overview The goal of this maturity model is to describe how Apache projects operate, in a concise and high-level way, and to provide a basic framework that projects may choose to use to evaluate themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Community Etiquette Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/etiquette.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/etiquette.html</guid>
      <description>The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) and our many Apache projects welcome all participants who are willing to respect our community guidelines. There are many behavior or etiquette guides for online communities out there; we have a few Apache-specific tips below.
Code of Conduct The ASF has adopted a Code of Conduct which covers interactions in all the online spaces that Apache projects use - email, issue trackers, wikis, websites, IRC, and the like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Conferences Calendar</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/calendars/conferences.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/calendars/conferences.html</guid>
      <description>Deprecated - See New Calendar instead This calendar is no longer maintained; please see this page instead.
This Calendar is maintained by the Apache Community Development Committee (ComDev), to have your event listed considered for addition please mail dev@community.apache.org. Note that to be listed in this calendar events must conform to the Third Party Event Branding Policy.
Upcoming events  List loading   This Calendar is also available as an iCal feed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache in GSoC</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/experiences.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/experiences.html</guid>
      <description>This is a place for collecting information about GSoC activities each year for historical tracking. It was started in 2012 so is missing plenty of detail in the early years. Your help filling it out would be appreciated.
2018 Overview  Students accepted: ? Students who passed final: 29  2017 Overview  Students accepted: ? Students who passed final: 27  2016 Overview  Students accepted: 49 Students who passed final: 35  2015 Overview  Students accepted: 56 Students who passed final: 47  2014 Overview  Students accepted: 42 Students who passed final: 35  2013 Overview  Students accepted: 51 Students who passed final: 44  2012 Overview  Students accepted: 41 Students who passed midterm: 40 26 projects mentoring (17 TLPs and 9 Podlings)  Participating TLPS are: Xerces, Pig, OODT, Hive, James, Tapestry, Ofbiz, Gora, Synapse, Derby, Axis, POI, Whirr, Lucene, Velocity, Libcloud, Xalan Participating Podlings are: ODF Toolkit, Airavata, Stanbol, Photark, Wookie, OpenMeetings, Nuvem, Hama, VXQuery    2012 Blogs  Scott Wilson: Wookie Mentor Pushpalanka: Wookie Student Mike McCandless: Lucene Mentor Bhathiya Jayasekara: Airavata Student OpenMeetings Mentors: Sebastian Wagner, Alexei Fedotov, Maxim Solodovnik - Students: Ankur Ankan, German Grekhov, Dmitry Zamula, Josh Dolitsky   2011 Overview  Students accepted: 40 Students who passed midterm: 38 Students who passed final: 36  2010 Overview  Students accepted: 44 Students who passed final: 39  2005 First year Apache participated</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Newcomer FAQs</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newbiefaq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newbiefaq.html</guid>
      <description>These answers to frequently asked questions may help newcomers to The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) and our many Apache projects understand how we work.
Index of Questions
 About The Apache Software Foundation  How do I find projects or technologies at the ASF? How are projects managed at the ASF? How do I learn about the way Apache Projects work? How do I ask a question about the ASF in general?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Related Event Calendars</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/calendars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/calendars/</guid>
      <description>This calendar lists major events relating to The Apache Software Foundation and our many Apache projects. We also have an automated listing of upcoming Apache-related Meetups (smaller events) available.
This Calendar is maintained by Apache Community Development volunteers (ComDev); to have your event listed considered for addition please mail dev@community.apache.org. Note that to be listed in this calendar events must already conform to the Third Party Event Branding Policy and have been approved by either the relevant Apache PMC or the Branding Committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache-related slides, videos and presentations</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers/slides.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/speakers/slides.html</guid>
      <description>This page contains links to presentations and other key papers about the ASF and how Apache projects work that you may find useful. Many of these have been presented at ApacheCon conferences or other open source conferences.
These presentations are available under permissive licenses; please see each individual presentation for license details. More tips and links for speakers are available.
Many Apache speakers post their slides to the SlideShare website, and the FeatherCast podcast offers audio recordings of many talks and interviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2017 Community Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-04.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-04.html</guid>
      <description>Apache Committer Newsletter, April 2017 Dear Apache Committer,
In this newsletter: committer resources you might not know about, Foundation news, and upcoming community events.
Thank you for your hard work on our Apache projects. You are the reason the Foundation exists, and your work is the reason we have the reputation we enjoy.
In our recent community survey, we heard from a lot of you that you want more information about what committer resources are available, how to connect with developers from other projects, and more information about what’s going on in the Foundation at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BoardReport</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/boardreport.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/boardreport.html</guid>
      <description>Top-level projects report to the board once a quarter, Incubator podlings usually monthly.
The ASF Board currently meets on the third Wednesday of every month, and projects need to report well in advance of that, as reports are reviewed before the meeting.
This page provides a simple template for board reports and should be read in conjunction with https://apache.org/foundation/board/reporting which contains additional information.
Reports need not be exhaustive, unless you are asking for assistance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ComDevBoardReports</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/comdevboardreports.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/comdevboardreports.html</guid>
      <description>This page contains records of the Apache Community Development Project board reports. The official record of these reports is the minutes of the appropriate board meeting, they are provided here for convenience.

Draft report for next meeting The following report is incomplete and draft only. It is being prepared for the next submission to the board. Submitted reports can be found further down the page.
DRAFT November 2012 Status report for the Apache Community Development Project The Community Development PMC is responsible for helping people become involved with Apache projects</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ComDevBoardResolution</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/comdevboardresolution.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/comdevboardresolution.html</guid>
      <description>The Apache Community Development Project was created in November 2009.
Board Resolution Creating the Apache Community Development ProjectEstablish the Apache Community Development Project  WHEREAS, the Board of Directors deems it to be in the best interests of the Foundation and consistent with the Foundation&#39;s purpose to establish a Project Management Committee charged with coordinating community development efforts. NOW, THEREFORE, BE IT RESOLVED, that a Project Management Committee (PMC), to be known as the &amp;quot;Apache Community Development Project&amp;quot;, be and hereby is established pursuant to Bylaws of the Foundation; and be it further RESOLVED, that the Apache Community Development Project be and hereby is responsible for helping people become involved with Apache projects; and be it further RESOLVED, that the office of Vice President, Apache Community Development Project, be and hereby is created, the person holding such office to serve at the direction of the Board of Directors as the chair of the Community Development PMC, and to have primary responsibility for management of the projects within the scope of the Apache Community Development project; and be it further RESOLVED, that the persons listed immediately below be and hereby are appointed to serve as the initial members of the Apache Community Development Project PMC: * Ross Gardler &amp;lt;rgardler@apache.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committer resources</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of useful Apache tools and services available for Apache projects and committers. This is a brief set of pointers or signposts to that information.
Apache Infrastructure Information The primary portals for Apache Infra questions - how Subversion/Git/Websites, etc. work at the ASF - are pages at apache.org/dev and infra.apache.org.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a committer, you can patch this very website yourself!
Decision making Decisions in Apache projects result from:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Development Mailing Lists</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/lists.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/lists.html</guid>
      <description>Almost everything at Apache uses a mailing list to get work done, including this Community Development project right here! People can send mail to the list, many other community members get the message, and someone will usually reply. Every mailing list at Apache is archived: most lists are archived publicly. That means that newcomers to a community can learn how decisions on a project were made in the past, because all the discussions a project had are archived from their mailing list discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Development: What we do</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Community Development: What We Do The Community Development (ComDev) project provides a wide array of information, FAQs, and help to newcomers and existing committers, and maintains a number of helpful tools.
 Community Development: What We Do  Mentoring for Individuals and Help Getting Around Mentoring for Projects Education + Outreach Diversity Conference Travel Assistance Tools and Code we Maintain Physical artifacts Book/Documentation Sprints   About This Website   Mentoring for Individuals and Help Getting Around  GSoC Contributors Guide Committers Guide Project Management Committees  Mentoring for Projects  Incubator Mentors - Many folks here are IPMC members or mentors, too TLPs and sub-projects Project Community Ombudsman - get community advice on dev@community  Education + Outreach  ApacheCon Partnered Industry Events (FOSDEM etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consensus Building</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/consensusBuilding.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/consensusBuilding.html</guid>
      <description>In some cases there is no obvious path to take, or you might be a new community, or a new member of an existing community. In these cases people will often need to build consensus by making proposals and eliciting responses.
We want to avoid unnecessary discussion and the creation of significant amounts of unnecessary mail that everyone in the community needs to read. That is not to say that we want to avoid constructive discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ContactPoints</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contactpoints.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contactpoints.html</guid>
      <description>If you have a question about anything Apache, the ComDev project is here to help.
To help us help you, try to direct your question to the right mailing list - our volunteer committers do all their work on mailing lists.
Community Questions Email questions about community or issues across multiple Apache projects to dev@community.apache.org - or see our detailed Mailing List How To page.
Technical Questions If you have a technical question about this website, or one of the tools that the ComDev project builds, email us at dev@community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to the Apache Software Foundation</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</guid>
      <description>This page is for people who are reasonably comfortable with open source development models but need a helping hand finding their way around the Apache Software Foundation and our way of developing software (commonly called &amp;ldquo;The Apache Way&amp;rdquo;). For those wishing to start from the very beginning, we have a newcomers page.
Project Independence And Policies While not all ASF projects practice all aspects of the Apache Way in the same way, there are a number of rules that Apache projects must follow – things like complying with PMC release voting, legal policy, brand policy, using mailing lists, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/decisionMaking.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/decisionMaking.html</guid>
      <description>The most important thing about engaging with any Apache project is that everyone is equal. All people with an opinion are entitled to express that opinion and, where appropriate, have it considered by the community.
To some the idea of having to establish consensus in a large and distributed team sounds inefficient and frustrating. Don&amp;rsquo;t despair though, The Apache Way has a set of simple processes to ensure things proceed at a good pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funding campaign disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/funding-disclaimer.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/funding-disclaimer.html</guid>
      <description>Some Apache committers have successfully run funding campaigns to work on their favorite Apache projects.
This is ok in principle but you have to make it clear that the campaign is your own thing, and avoid any confusion about the role of the ASF and how its projects work.
This page gives a few examples of that.
If you have any question about this, feel free to ask on our dev@community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gettingStarted/101.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gettingStarted/101.html</guid>
      <description>Where do I start? If you have no idea where to start your engagement with an Apache project, this is the page for you.
Finding the right project The key to working on projects at Apache (and on any open source project, for that matter) is to have a personal reason for being involved. You might be trying to solve a day job issue, you might be looking to learn a new technology or you might simply want to do something fun in your free time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gsoc.html</guid>
      <description>Currently happening  We are now collecting ideas for GSoC 2021   Google is sponsoring the 2021 Summer of Code and The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) [not yet] registered as a mentoring organization. This page is your entry point to the ASF GSoC program. Please watch this page for updates concerning our participating in 2021.

Students: read this  Learn about GSoC Decide if you are eligible for GSoC?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC admins</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc-admin-tasks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gsoc-admin-tasks.html</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive guide to being the GSoC admins for the ASF
List of duties:
 Make sure the ASF has an extensive list of project ideas ready shortly after Google announces the program (around end of January). Projects are required to create JIRA issues for their ideas and label them with &amp;ldquo;gsoc&amp;lt;year&amp;gt;&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;mentor&amp;rdquo;. If a project doesn&amp;rsquo;t use JIRA, have them create the ideas in the COMDEV JIRA project. Create a JIRA filter for these ideas to be used in the application (see next).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guide to being a mentor</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/guide-to-being-a-mentor.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/guide-to-being-a-mentor.html</guid>
      <description>Submitting ideas to the mentoring programme We invite all ASF projects to submit their ideas for consideration in the ASF mentoring programme. Any Apache member and experienced committers can submit ideas via JIRA (if your project does not use JIRA you can use the Comdev Issue Tracker For GSoC Tasks. We are looking for as many interesting projects as we can come up with.

Summary  Add an issue to JIRA (if your project does not use JIRA you can use the Comdev Issue Tracker For GSoC Tasks  Add sub-tasks if necessary   Label the main issue with &amp;ldquo;mentor&amp;rdquo; (these will show up at the ASF-wide list of issues) Label the main issue with &amp;ldquo;gsoc2021&amp;rdquo; if appropriate (these will show up at https://s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: Write A Mentor Request Email</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentor-request-mail.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentor-request-mail.html</guid>
      <description>Having identified a Top Level Project (TLP) and an issue you would like to work on, it is a good idea to introduce yourself to the project community and outline your plans for tackling the issue. This lets the community know you are working on the issue and gives the community an early opportunity to help course correct your proposal, if necessary (which can save you lots of time).
Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of what your first email might look like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lazy Consensus</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/lazyConsensus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/lazyConsensus.html</guid>
      <description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;lazy consensus&amp;rdquo; is very important in your project. Lazy consensus means that when you are convinced that you know what the community would like to see happen, you can assume that you have consensus in favor of the proposed work and and get on with it. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to insist people discuss and/or approve your plan, and you certainly don&amp;rsquo;t need to call a vote to get approval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/links.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/links.html</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of links to information that&amp;rsquo;s relevant to the Apache Way and Open Source in general.
Note that most of these links point to websites that are outside of the control of the Apache Software Foundation. Please contact their respective authors for more information or questions. General discussion on the dev@community.a.o list is fine of course.
Books  Producing Open Source Software - by Karl Fogel  Blog posts  Apache - the Switzerland of Open Source?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listing yourself as a Potential Speaker</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers/speakers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/speakers/speakers.html</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re an Apache committer, and you&amp;rsquo;re interested in speaking about Apache Technologies, Apache Projects or the Apache Software Foundation as a whole, we&amp;rsquo;d encourage you to get involved and list yourself in our speaker application!
Finding Speakers If you are organising an event and looking for speakers, please see the Apache Speakers homepage for details.
Listing yourself as a Potential Speaker To list yourself as someone interested in being an Apache Speaker, there are two steps involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LocalMentors</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/localmentors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/localmentors.html</guid>
      <description>The Local Mentors project aims to allow people getting started in Apache (both within the Formal Mentoring Program , and everyone else) to meet up with existing Apache developers in their area.

Why? When you&amp;rsquo;re getting involved in a new open source project, it can be a little daunting. You engage in the mailing lists with people from all around the world. You solve bugs with people in different time zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2017 Community Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-05.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-05.html</guid>
      <description>Committer Resources
(So that we didn&amp;rsquo;t put them all in the first edition)
If you blog about anything Apache related, you might want to know about http://planet.apache.org/committers/ - the Apache committer blog aggregator. It’s valuable in seeing what the rest of the Apache community is working on. To add yourself to the planet, edit the file https://svn.apache.org/repos/asf/planet/committers.ini in svn. It’s preferable if you use an ‘apache’ tag to separate out the stuff that is relevant to the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentee Ranking Process</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentee-ranking-process.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentee-ranking-process.html</guid>
      <description>This page describes the ranking process The Apache Software Foundation uses to evaluate mentee proposals.
The ranking process makes sure the most promising applicants get a mentor with an ASF project. The goal is not to identify the &amp;ldquo;best&amp;rdquo; projects for the ASF, but the best mentees who have applied to the ASF.
Remember, mentoring is all about the mentee and open source as a whole. It is not about the mentors or their projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentor Programme Application</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentorprogrammeapplication.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentorprogrammeapplication.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring Programme Application Procedure Applying for the Apache Mentoring Programme is simple. This page will take you through the steps:

Creating a proposal and finding a mentor  Find the project you are interested in (see our FAQ for some guidance on how to do this) Examine the projects issue tracker to find bugs that need fixing or features that need implementing that you feel you can tackle Join the projects mailing list and post an introduction mail (something like this mentor request mail will do nicely).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/</guid>
      <description>Mentoring A major job of Community Development is mentoring. Mentoring is the process of actively bringing someone along in a discipline - investing your time into influencing the future. Time spent mentoring today will pay off for years to come.
Anyone can be a mentor. You just have to take a moment to encourage someone else to participate.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some concrete ways you can provide mentoring to other members of your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring a new committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/committer.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/committer.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring a new committer So I&amp;rsquo;m a committer now. What&amp;rsquo;s next? What rights do I have now that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have before? What are the social conventions around making a commit?
These things vary from one project to another, so clearly documenting them for your particular project is critical.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the basics that are true across (almost) all Apache projects.
TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring a new PMC member</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/pmc.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/pmc.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring a new PMC member So I&amp;rsquo;m a PMC member now. What does this mean? What rights do I have now that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have before? What conversations belong on the private list, as opposed to the public list.
These things vary a little from one project to another, so clearly documenting them for your particular project is critical. And specifically assigning a PMC mentor to new PMC members can greatly help that new member get up to speed, and prevent problems in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring Mentors</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/mentor.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/mentor.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring Mentors The job of a mentor is to reproduce - spread the work load. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve mentored someone, you need to encourage them to become a mentor themselves. Here&amp;rsquo;s some ways you can do that.
 Point out people that need a little help Encourage them to answer a question rather than answering it yourself &amp;hellip;  TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring: First Patch</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/firstpatch.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoring/firstpatch.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring: First Patch A beginner&amp;rsquo;s first patch on a project can be an intimidating and frustrating experience. Clearly documenting the entire process from checkout to accepted patch greatly lowers the barrier for a new contributor, and makes it more likely that they&amp;rsquo;ll come back for their second patch.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some tips on how to do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MentoringProgramme</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoringprogramme.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoringprogramme.html</guid>
      <description>Many projects in the ASF are able to provide mentors for newcomers. In fact, most projects are happy to assist newcomers to their projects as part of their normal operations. However, some people are looking for more structure. The Mentor Programme of the The Apache Software Foundation provides additional support and structure for people looking to make an initial contribution to an ASF project.
The mentoring programme is not here to teach you to write documentation or code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MentorProgrammeFormalEducation</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentorprogrammeformaleducation.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentorprogrammeformaleducation.html</guid>
      <description>Mentoring in Formal Education Some mentees will wish to participate in the Mentoring Programme as part of a formal education course. In these cases there will be additional requirements and process steps to ensure that the mentees can be evaluated by their tutor. This section describes these additional requirements and process.

Overview Projects are defined by the students tutor in consultation with the TLP community/mentors and the student. They will need to be isolated enough from other ongoing work to ensure that success/failure to deliver is not dependent on someone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newcommitter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newcommitter.html</guid>
      <description>Identifying potential new committers, calling a vote for their recognition as a committer and processing the relevant documents is something to which the whole community can contribute.
Each project has a different approach to managing new committers. This page describes a common process found in many Apache projects. It also provides drafts for the various communications that are necessary.
 Guidelines for assessing new candidates for committership  Ability to work cooperatively with peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Community Development Newsletter The Community Development project has started a monthly newsletter, to keep the larger Apache Community informed of what&amp;rsquo;s happening across the Foundation. If you would like to contribute content to this newsletter, please join the ComDev mailing list where this message is drafted.
 April 2017  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilot Mentoring Programme with India ICFOSS</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/mentoringprogramme-icfoss-pilot.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/mentoringprogramme-icfoss-pilot.html</guid>
      <description>Note that this information is about a pilot program that happened back in 2013.
 The ASF has been participating in many mentoring initiatives, and it&amp;rsquo;s now partnering in a pilot project with India ICFOSS to provide mentoring for undergraduate and graduate students that have interest in learning how to participate in open source communities at ASF.
The mentoring programme is not here to teach you to write documentation or code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Independence</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/projectIndependence.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/projectIndependence.html</guid>
      <description>While not all ASF projects practice all aspects of the Apache Way in the same way, there are a number of rules and policies that Apache projects must follow – things like complying with PMC release voting, legal policy, brand policy, using mailing lists, etc., which are documented in various places.
A community is not merely a set of rules; it is also a set of behaviors that the participants express when interacting within that community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Requirements for organizers of small Apache-related events</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/events/small-events.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/events/small-events.html</guid>
      <description>Approval of small Apache-related events The Community Development PMC is responsible for assisting with the organisation and promotion of all Apache events.
Organizers of Apache-related events need approval for using the Apache trademarks in their event brandings.
The main steps are:
a) Get approval from the PMCs of the projects that your event is about.
b) Abide by the Apache branding rules.
c) Once brand use is approved by the respective PMCs, inform the community development PMC of your event, including references to PMCs approval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking about Apache, our Projects and our Community</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/speakers/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for speakers for an event, or are a speaker looking for materials, this is the place for you.
If you are seeking to organise an Apache-branded event, you must ensure your activities conform to the Third Party Event Branding Policy. Once you have verified you are in conformance, please consider adding your event to the events calendar.
Finding speakers You can use our &amp;ldquo;Find People&amp;rdquo; application to find speakers willing and able to talk about The Apache Software Foundation and its projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use the Comdev Issue Tracker For GSoC Tasks</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/use-the-comdev-issue-tracker-for-gsoc-tasks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/use-the-comdev-issue-tracker-for-gsoc-tasks.html</guid>
      <description>If your project does not use the ASF Jira for issue tracking, you can use the Community Development Jira project to record your GSoC tasks.
 Add tasks to the Comdev project Ensure you add the labels gsoc2021, mentor and _YOUR_PROJECT_NAME_ Your issues will appear in the list of projects We use the label _YOUR_PROJECT_NAME_ to map COMDEV issues to the real project when we create the ideas list  Please contact dev@community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voting</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/committers/voting.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/committers/voting.html</guid>
      <description>Occasionally a &amp;ldquo;feel&amp;rdquo; for consensus is not enough. Sometimes we need to have a measurable consensus, for example, when voting to invite new committers or to approve a release.
Preparing for a Vote Before calling a vote it is important to ensure that the community has time to discuss the issue before voting. To do this, post an email to the list indicating the intention to call a vote and the options available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome, Apache newcomers!</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newcomers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newcomers/</guid>
      <description>In this section we&amp;rsquo;ll help you take your first steps as an open source developer in one of our many Apache project communities. As an all-volunteer run organization, Apache and the many Apache projects rely on people like you stepping up to help out.
 Where do I start? - a guide to your first engagement with an Apache project How should I behave? - etiquette and codes of conduct at Apache What can I work on?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>