<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>contacts on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/contacts.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in contacts on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/contacts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Community Development Mailing Lists</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/lists.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/lists.html</guid>
      <description>Almost everything and everyone at Apache use email lists to get work done, including this Community Development project right here! When people send email to a list, many other community members get the message, and someone usually provides a useful reply. Every email list at Apache is archived: most lists are archived publicly. That means that newcomers to a community can learn how decisions on a project have been made in the past, because all the email discussions a project has had are archived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact points</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contactpoints.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contactpoints.html</guid>
      <description>If you have a question about anything Apache, the ComDev project is here to help.
To help us help you, try to direct your question to the right mailing list - our volunteer committers do all their work on mailing lists.
Community Questions &amp;para; Email questions about community or issues across multiple Apache projects to dev@community.apache.org - or see our detailed Mailing List How To page.
Technical Questions &amp;para; If you have a technical question about this website, or one of the tools that the ComDev project builds, email us at dev@community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
