<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributors on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributors on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/contributors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Community Etiquette Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/etiquette.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/etiquette.html</guid>
      <description>The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) and our many Apache projects welcome all participants who are willing to respect our community guidelines. There are many behavior or etiquette guides for online communities out there; we have a few Apache-specific tips below.
Code of Conduct The ASF has adopted a Code of Conduct which covers interactions in all the online spaces that Apache projects use - email, issue trackers, wikis, websites, IRC, and the like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to the Apache Software Foundation</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</guid>
      <description>This page is intended for those people who are reasonably comfortable with open source development models but need a helping hand finding their way around The Apache Software Foundation and our way of developing software (commonly called &amp;ldquo;The Apache Way&amp;rdquo;). For those wishing to start from the very beginning we have a newcomers page too.
Project Independence And Policies While not all aspects of the Apache Way are practiced the same way by all projects at the ASF, there are a number of rules that Apache projects are required to follow – things like complying with PMC release voting, legal policy, brand policy, using mailing lists, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>