<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributing to the Apache Software Foundation on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributing to the Apache Software Foundation on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/contributors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ASF Community Etiquette Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/etiquette.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/etiquette.html</guid>
      <description>The ASF and our many projects welcome all participants. Before you begin, it is important to review and respect our community guidelines. We have a few ASF-specific tips below.
Code of Conduct &amp;para; The ASF has adopted a Code of Conduct which covers interactions in all the online spaces that ASF projects use - email, issue trackers, wikis, websites, IRC, and the like. ASF projects are made up of volunteers, and we work to ensure that all productive contributions are welcomed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/becomingacommitter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/becomingacommitter.html</guid>
      <description>Read the mailing list Contribute code (and other things) End user support Documentation Review PRs and tickets Be visible Test, and vote on releases (non-binding) Give talks Disclaimer &amp;para; Nothing in this post should be construed as a guarantee. You can do everything listed here, for years, and still not become a committer. This is because the decision is made by individuals on the project PMC, who do things for their own reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailing lists</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/mailing-lists.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/mailing-lists.html</guid>
      <description>The ASF has a long tradition of using mailing lists as the primary communication format in projects. This is not merely because we&amp;rsquo;ve always done it that way, but is an intentional decision for the health and sustainability of our communities.
Inclusion and transparency &amp;para; Mailing lists ensure that all members of the community can participate on a level field, regardless of time zone or availability, whereas synchronous communication platforms (IRC, Slack, Discord, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
