<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Management Committees on ASF Community Development</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Management Committees on ASF Community Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/pmc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding Committers</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-committers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-committers.html</guid>
      <description>Identifying potential new committers, calling a vote for their recognition as a committer and processing the relevant documents are tasks to which the whole community can contribute.
Each project has a different approach to managing new committers. This page describes a common process found in many Apache projects. It also provides draft templates for the various communications that are necessary.
Some of the PMCs automatically make committers PMC members. The templates below have conditional [if] clauses for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding PMC members</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-pmc-members.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-pmc-members.html</guid>
      <description>This document describes a typical Apache project&amp;rsquo;s process for handling the vote to add a new PMC (Project Management Committee) member - when it is separate from becoming committer.
Templates mentioned in the process appear [#NewPMCMember-EmailTemplates](later in this document). If your PMC adds automatically committers as PMC members, the process for doing both at the same time is described in the New committer advice.
The Contributor Ladder helps explain different roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Growth</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/community-growth.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/community-growth.html</guid>
      <description>Building a thriving project community requires intentional effort. This guide provides practical strategies to attract contributors to your project, and engage them in it.
Publish a roadmap Periodically publish the open issue list Clearly document contribution processes Publish your contributor ladder Engage with big users Be transparent about project risk Come talk to us Publish a roadmap &amp;para; While volunteers choose their own contributions, providing direction helps them find meaningful ways to get involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New PMC Members</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/new-member.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/new-member.html</guid>
      <description>Congratulations on your invitation to join a project PMC! Here&amp;rsquo;s what you should do next.
Joining an ASF Project Management Committee represents more than recognition of your contributions. You take on a new level of responsibility for the project&amp;rsquo;s health and sustainability. The Board of Directors relies on you to provide oversight of the project code and community.
Join the conversation &amp;para; Subscribe to the PMC/Private mailing list if you haven&amp;rsquo;t already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMC Chair</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/chair.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/chair.html</guid>
      <description>The PMC Chair serves as the project&amp;rsquo;s voice to the board and handles quarterly reporting.
While typically a senior, respected community leader, the Chair is not the project leader but a peer among PMC members, with the same voting rights and authority as other PMC members, who has accepted additional secretarial and spokesperson responsibilities.
The Chair must familiarize themselves with the assigned duties of the role.
Secretarial duties Reporting Moderating discussion Selecting a new Chair See also: Secretarial duties &amp;para; The Chair is responsible for completing the necessary processes when the PMC adds committers and members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMC Reporting</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/reporting.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/reporting.html</guid>
      <description>Each PMC must submit a quarterly report to the Board of Directors according to a schedule set by the Board.
You can find your project&amp;rsquo;s reporting schedule by visiting the committee&amp;rsquo;s page on projects.apache.org. You will also receive a reminder from the Secretary a few weeks prior to your report&amp;rsquo;s due date.
The official record of PMC reporting schedules is the file committee-info.txt (requires password authentication).
Writing a report &amp;para; While you may use the reporter tool to draft your report, avoid submitting auto-generated content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMC Responsibilities</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/responsibilities.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/responsibilities.html</guid>
      <description>The Project Management Committee (PMC) oversees the project, including technical decisions, ensuring compliance with ASF standards, adding new members, and approving releases.
Conducting Business Protecting your brand Making a release Ensuring Project Health Adding Community Members Conducting Business &amp;para; The PMC must conduct all business on the public developers&amp;rsquo; mailing list, maintaining full community visibility.
Every PMC has a private@ list reserved for confidential matters such as discussing proposed committers, potential PMC members, or security issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
