<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Management Committees on ASF Community Development</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Management Committees on ASF Community Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/pmc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding Committers</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-committers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-committers.html</guid>
      <description>Identifying potential new committers, calling a vote for their recognition as a committer and processing the relevant documents are tasks to which the whole community can contribute.
Each project has a different approach to managing new committers. This page describes a common process found in many Apache projects. It also provides draft templates for the various communications that are necessary.
Some of the PMCs automatically make committers PMC members. The templates below have conditional [if] clauses for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding PMC members</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-pmc-members.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-pmc-members.html</guid>
      <description>This document describes a typical Apache project&amp;rsquo;s process for handling the vote to add a new PMC (Project Management Committee) member - when it is separate from becoming committer.
Templates mentioned in the process appear [#NewPMCMember-EmailTemplates](later in this document). If your PMC adds automatically committers as PMC members, the process for doing both at the same time is described in the New committer advice.
The Contributor Ladder helps explain different roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Growth</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/community-growth.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/community-growth.html</guid>
      <description>Growing your project community takes work. This document makes practical suggestions of how to encourage people to get involved in your project.
Publish a roadmap Periodically publish the open issue list Clearly document contribution processes Publish your contributor ladder Engage with big users Be transparent about project risk Come talk to us Publish a roadmap &amp;para; Volunteers can work on whatever they want, and so we have a tendency to not want to tell them what to work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New PMC Members</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/new-member.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/new-member.html</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been invited to join a project PMC? Congratulations! What should you do now?
Being part of an ASF Project Management Committee is more than just an acknowledgement of your contributions. It&amp;rsquo;s a new level of responsibility for the project&amp;rsquo;s health and sustainability. The Board of Directors is relying on you to provide oversight of the project code, and project community
Join the conversation &amp;para; If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, you need to subscribe to the PMC/Private mailing list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMC Chair</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/chair.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/chair.html</guid>
      <description>The PMC Chair acts as the voice of the project to the board, and is responsible for filing a quarterly report. They are not the project leader, but are a peer of the other PMC members, who has been selected, for a time, to take the role of secretary and spokesperson.
The PMC Chair is not the de-facto project leader. While they are usually a senior, well-respected member of the community, they are a peer, with a few additional duties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMC Reporting</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/reporting.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/reporting.html</guid>
      <description>A PMC is required to file a report to the Board of Directors every quarter, on a schedule determined by the Board.
You can find your project&amp;rsquo;s reporting schedule on projects.apache.org. You will also receive a reminder from the Secretary a few weeks prior to your report&amp;rsquo;s due date.
The official record of PMC reporting schedules is the file committee-info.txt (requires password authentication).
Writing a report &amp;para; The report to the board is expected to contain certain sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMC Responsibilities</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/responsibilities.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/responsibilities.html</guid>
      <description>The Project Management Committee (PMC) is responsible for the oversight of the project, including technical decisions, ensuring that the project is operating in accordance with ASF norms, adding new members to the project, and voting on releases.
Conducting Business Protecting your brand Making a release Ensuring Project Health Adding Community Members Conducting Business &amp;para; The PMC is expected to conduct all of its business on the public developers mailing list, in the full view of the community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
