<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speakers on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speakers on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/speakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apache-related slides, videos and presentations</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers/slides.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/speakers/slides.html</guid>
      <description>This page contains links to presentations and other key papers about the ASF and how Apache projects work that you may find useful. Many of these have been presented at ApacheCon conferences or other open source conferences.
These presentations are available under permissive licenses; please see each individual presentation for license details.
Many Apache speakers post their slides to the SlideShare website, and the FeatherCast podcast offers audio recordings of many talks and interviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listing yourself as a Potential Speaker</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers/speakers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/speakers/speakers.html</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re an Apache committer interested in speaking about Apache Technologies, Apache Projects or the Apache Software Foundation as a whole, we encourage you to get involved and list yourself in our speaker application!
Finding Speakers &amp;para; If you are organising an event and looking for speakers, see the Apache Speakers homepage for details.
Listing yourself as a potential speaker &amp;para; To list yourself as someone interested in being an Apache speaker, there are two steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking about Apache, our Projects and our Community</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/speakers/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for speakers for an event, or are a speaker looking for materials, this is the place for you.
If you are seeking to organise an Apache-branded event, you must ensure your activities conform to the Third Party Event Branding Policy. Once you have verified you are in conformance, please consider adding your event to the events calendar.
Finding speakers &amp;para; You can use our &amp;ldquo;Find People&amp;rdquo; application to find speakers willing and able to talk about The Apache Software Foundation and its projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
