<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>collaboration on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/collaboration.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in collaboration on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/collaboration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Apache Projects Use Consensus</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/blog/how_apache_projects_use_consensus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/blog/how_apache_projects_use_consensus.html</guid>
      <description>The Apache Software Foundation exists to provide legal and technological infrastructure for open source projects. By and large, the Foundation leaves the individual project communities to make their own choices about their development process. There are some constraints that result from the fundamental legal umbrella held by the Foundation. For the Foundation to protect contributors, projects must respect the rules regarding IP management and releases. A more interesting set of constraints, however, stems from the Foundation&amp;rsquo;s commitment to Open Source software development as a communal process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What makes Apache projects different?</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/blog/what_makes_apache_projects_different.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/blog/what_makes_apache_projects_different.html</guid>
      <description>Sharing a code repository with some other programmers might seem enough to create an open source project; the Apache Software Foundation goes further and focuses on making projects sustainable in the long term, and ensuring that our code is legally clean.
This means that our projects have to follow a (small) number of rules, and a number of best practices have been established over the years.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick description of how Apache projects are born and live on - some of the items below are derived from the ASF&amp;rsquo;s bylaws (http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
