<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>election on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/election.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in election on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding PMC members</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-pmc-members.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/adding-pmc-members.html</guid>
      <description>The PMC is responsible for identifying individuals who should be added to the PMC. This is a critical part of the long-term health and sustainability of a project, and ensures that contributors to the project have a voice in the project&amp;rsquo;s roadmap.
Who should be a PMC member? Nominating, discussion, and voting What to do when a new PMC member is elected Note: Formal policy/process doc is here: https://www.apache.org/dev/pmc.html#newpmc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Committer</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newcommitter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newcommitter.html</guid>
      <description>Identifying potential new committers, calling a vote for their recognition as a committer and processing the relevant documents are tasks to which the whole community can contribute.
Each project has a different approach to managing new committers. This page describes a common process found in many Apache projects. It also provides drafts for the various communications that are necessary.
Guidelines for assessing new candidates for committership Ability to work cooperatively with peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New PMC Members</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/pmc/new-member.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/pmc/new-member.html</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been invited to join a project PMC? Congratulations! What should you do now?
&amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;lt; HEAD &amp;para; Being part of an ASF Project Management Committee is more than just an acknowledgement of your contributions. It&amp;rsquo;s a new level of responsibility for the project&amp;rsquo;s health and sustainability. The Board of Directors is relying on you to provide oversight of the project code, and project community
Join the conversation &amp;para; If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, you need to subscribe to the PMC/Private mailing list.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
