<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>faq on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/tags/faq.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in faq on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/tags/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apache Newcomer FAQs</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newbiefaq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newbiefaq.html</guid>
      <description>These answers to frequently asked questions may help newcomers to The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) and our many Apache projects understand how we work.
Index of Questions
About The Apache Software Foundation How do I find projects or technologies at the ASF? How are projects managed at the ASF? How do I ask a question about the ASF in general? How do I get user support for an Apache project? Getting involved with Apache projects How do I choose an Apache project to work on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Development: What we do</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Community Development: What We Do &amp;para; The Community Development (ComDev) project provides a wide array of information, FAQs, and help to newcomers and existing committers, and maintains a number of helpful tools.
Community Development: What We Do Mentoring for Individuals and Help Getting Around Mentoring for Projects Education + Outreach Diversity Conference Travel Assistance Tools and Code we Maintain Physical artifacts About This Website Mentoring for Individuals and Help Getting Around &amp;para; GSoC Contributors Guide Committers Guide Project Management Committees Mentoring for Projects &amp;para; Incubator Mentors - Many folks here are IPMC members or mentors, too Get community advice on dev@community Education + Outreach &amp;para; ApacheCon Partnered Industry Events (FOSDEM etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to the Apache Software Foundation</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/contributors/</guid>
      <description>This page is for people who are reasonably comfortable with open source development models but need a helping hand finding their way around the Apache Software Foundation and our way of developing software (commonly called &amp;ldquo;The Apache Way&amp;rdquo;). For those wishing to start from the very beginning, we have a newcomers page.
Project Independence And Policies &amp;para; While not all ASF projects practice all aspects of the Apache Way in the same way, there are a number of rules that Apache projects must follow – things like complying with PMC release voting, legal policy, brand policy, using mailing lists, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
