<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newsletters on Apache Comdev</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/newsletter.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newsletters on Apache Comdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/newsletter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2017 Community Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-04.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-04.html</guid>
      <description>Apache Committer Newsletter, April 2017 Dear Apache Committer,
In this newsletter: committer resources you might not know about, Foundation news, and upcoming community events.
Thank you for your hard work on our Apache projects. You are the reason the Foundation exists, and your work is the reason we have the reputation we enjoy.
In our recent community survey, we heard from a lot of you that you want more information about what committer resources are available, how to connect with developers from other projects, and more information about what’s going on in the Foundation at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2017 Community Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-05.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/2017-05.html</guid>
      <description>Committer Resources
(So that we didn&amp;rsquo;t put them all in the first edition)
If you blog about anything Apache related, you might want to know about http://planet.apache.org/committers/ - the Apache committer blog aggregator. It’s valuable in seeing what the rest of the Apache community is working on. To add yourself to the planet, edit the file https://svn.apache.org/repos/asf/planet/committers.ini in svn. It’s preferable if you use an ‘apache’ tag to separate out the stuff that is relevant to the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Community Development Newsletter The Community Development project has started a monthly newsletter, to keep the larger Apache Community informed of what&amp;rsquo;s happening across the Foundation. If you would like to contribute content to this newsletter, please join the ComDev mailing list where this message is drafted.
 April 2017  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>