<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GSoC on ASF Community Development</title>
    <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GSoC on ASF Community Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://community.apache.org/gsoc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GSoC admins</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/gsoc-admin-tasks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/gsoc-admin-tasks.html</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive guide to being a GSoC admin for the ASF
List of duties:
Make sure the ASF has an extensive list of project ideas ready shortly after Google announces the program (around the end of January). Projects must create Jira issues for their ideas and label them with gsoc2024; and mentor. If a project doesn&amp;rsquo;t use Jira, have them create the ideas in the GSOC Jira project. Create a Jira filter for these ideas to use in the application (see next).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guide to being a mentor</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/guide-to-being-a-mentor.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/guide-to-being-a-mentor.html</guid>
      <description>Submitting ideas to the mentoring programme &amp;para; We invite all ASF projects to submit their ideas for consideration in the ASF mentoring programme. Any Apache member and experienced committers can submit ideas via Jira (if your project does not use Jira you can use the Comdev GSoC Issue Tracker For GSoC Tasks. We are looking for as many interesting projects as we can come up with.
Important Steps &amp;para; Add an issue to Jira (if your project does not use Jira you can use the Comdev GSoC Issue Tracker For GSoC Tasks Add sub-tasks if necessary Label the main issue with &amp;ldquo;mentor&amp;rdquo; (these will show up at the ASF-wide list of issues) Label the main issue with &amp;ldquo;gsoc2024&amp;rdquo; if appropriate (these will show up at GSoC 2024 Ideas) Size of project Starting in 2024 there are 3 types of projects available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentee Ranking Process</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/mentee-ranking-process.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/mentee-ranking-process.html</guid>
      <description>This page describes the ranking process The Apache Software Foundation uses to evaluate mentee proposals.
The ranking process makes sure the most promising applicants get a mentor with an ASF project. The goal is not to identify the &amp;ldquo;best&amp;rdquo; projects for the ASF, but the best mentees who have applied to the ASF.
Remember, mentoring is all about the mentee and open source as a whole. It is not about the mentors or their projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use the Comdev Issue Tracker For GSoC Tasks</title>
      <link>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/use-the-comdev-gsoc-issue-tracker-for-gsoc-tasks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://community.apache.org/gsoc/use-the-comdev-gsoc-issue-tracker-for-gsoc-tasks.html</guid>
      <description>If your project does not use the ASF Jira for issue tracking, you can use the ComDev GSoC Jira project to record your GSoC tasks.
Add tasks to the GSOC project Ensure you add the labels gsoc2024, mentor and _YOUR_PROJECT_NAME_ Your issues will appear in the list of projects We use the label _YOUR_PROJECT_NAME_ to map COMDEV issues to the real project when we create the ideas list Please contact dev@community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
